It's the 10th day.
If they don't get back here soon, then all of their data is going to be erased.
Right. We'll just have to wait for Gorenu to contact us.
Yes! Got it!
Hey, check it out! I've got this down!
Can I start to concentrate on emitter training now?
No way!
You might have gotten pretty close, but you're still off by a tenth of a second.
Your goal is to be within a hundredth of a second.
Now, begin!
Attention! Another player has cast contact on you.
We'll be right back.
You're right back.
Don't forget to show up.
It's Garenu. Sorry for the wait.
What's going on?
It's been almost 240 hours since Team Titsgera left, right?
Yeah.
I can tell you right now they won't be returning.
Why not?
Gintryu's team has started camping out at the start point.
We decided beforehand that they wouldn't return to the game until I sent them in all clear.
It was something of a safety precaution.
Understood. But their card data will disappear, right?
I'm holding on to all the cards of value.
Doesn't that just make it obvious that they have allies?
They'll notice none of the four have anything important.
They left the game at 3.05 ten days ago. Isn't that right?
Yeah. Only five more minutes till their card data is completely wiped. They basically quit.
We'll wait until 3.10 just to be safe.
All right. But do you really think they've given up?
Absolutely. Why else would they take off with Batera and run?
It looks like it was just a desperate attempt to keep us from getting the reward money.
Maybe you're right. But those guys have spent years collecting those 96 cards.
Besides, why would Batera call off his guards? It doesn't make any sense to me.
Yeah, but so what? Something probably happened.
Well, there's no point in speculating about it now.
Oh, look. 3.10 already. Time's up, I guess.
Yeah! Bye-bye, Tezgera!
Fake?
That's right. We switched several of their cards with fake ones. About 30 of the total 96 of them they have.
I'm actually holding the 96. For such a cautious guy, this is the biggest gamble of Tezgera's life.
So, I just want to make sure it pays off. And I'm really sorry, but I'm not going to be able to help you guys face Team Genthru.
No problem. But when do you want us to give you the card?
We can wait until you've defeated Genthru. Good luck, okay?
Now we'll go after those brats. It wasn't in the plan, but we can get Strip of Beach from them without too much trouble.
But first, we need more copies of a company.
Okay.
They're on the move! Hey, where are you guys right now?
Near Soframi.
Looks like they're all heading to Masadora. And as soon as they've got everything ready, I'm sure they'll be coming for you.
Are you ready?
All set here. You've all been a big help, thanks.
We need more time, but we have no choice. It's up to Gon now.
Gon! Did you let our conversation distract you from your current objective?
Just tell me what this is about.
I hope you'll forgive me, but I took the liberty of picking this up.
Is this your daughter? Or granddaughter, perhaps?
She was my lover.
She'd been in the hospital.
She'd been comatose for some time.
A few days ago, she passed away in her sleep.
I suppose it was because she didn't want people to think she was only after my money, but she returned every expensive gift I gave her.
Every single one.
But she loved this picture frame I clumsily made myself.
All we ever needed was each other, and we swore that we would never be apart.
Until the accident, when she fell into a deep sleep, never to awaken again.
Honestly, she just looked like she was only sleeping.
And it was then that I first heard about Greed Island.
And if I could only beat that game, I could obtain the one item I needed most.
It was like a dream come true.
I was fully prepared to spend my entire fortune on copies of that game.
But now, it's all over.
It doesn't matter anymore.
The Brats have four copies of a company.
We have six ourselves. Ready?
Hell yeah! You just say the word.
I'll take the kid who has the spiky black hair.
Assuming that we have to resort to force, that is.
Sub, take the cat-eyed one.
Bara, the girl.
Accompany on! Goon!
What do you want?
No need to be hostile.
Let's just make a deal.
With you? We're not interested.
Right. Don't let them notice we've been waiting for them.
They can't know we're fully prepared.
It's not a bad deal, you know.
In fact, it's so good that even Tezgera agreed to it.
What is it?
Curious now?
Don't move! You can talk from over there!
Yes. Very good.
We have to make it seem like we're weak and at a disadvantage.
We must try to create the impression that we only just arrived here
after being cornered in a chase.
It's actually surprisingly simple.
We'll beat the game on everyone's behalf.
Then everyone returns to the real world and splits Patera's reward.
I find that hard to believe.
We've had a little change of heart.
And Tezgera and the others have already left the game.
Yeah.
But that still doesn't prove that he agreed to your offer.
Yes, that's true.
Then you'd rather die here?
Just shut up and give us all your cards!
Otherwise, we'll kill all of you!
Finally showing your true colors, huh?
Look!
Company on!
To Sofrabi!
Hmm.
Three more times.
Two more times.
Only one more time.
Return on!
Masadora!
Masadora?
Are they trying to obtain more spell cards?
They might try to reach the real world through the harbor.
Accompany on!
Go!
They're not here.
Are they concealing their presence?
Check the store.
Don't want them getting their hands on any spell cards.
They haven't been here.
Maybe they took off for the harbor.
We have no choice.
Accompany on!
Go!
Don't lose sight of them!
We're completely out of accompanies!
Now, why don't you give up and hand over your cards?
You're crazy!
We'll never let you have them!
Everything is going as planned.
They want to fight us one-on-one.
If you want our cards, come and get them!
Wait, what?
Damn it!
Nice.
Now we just need to separate them little by little.
Bisky!
Get out of here now!
I-I...
I said run!
Stop!
You're not getting away!
I'm counting on you two.
Sorry, kid, but you're all mine now!
I-I...
So tell me...
You do know that I'm the bomber, don't you?
I heard it from Tezgyera!
Oh?
I see. And who told you how my ability works then?
Incredible. All it took was that one moment, and he figured out exactly why I'm so wary.
And why. That can only come from battle experience.
Not too many people know of my ability. And even fewer who have survived long enough to tell anyone.
Fuck!
I can't let him take control.
Look, I really hate the idea of taking cards from other people by force. So promise me right now!
Whichever of us surrenders first has to give up all his cards to the winner, okay?
I think you might have the wrong idea. You're in no position to be making demands.
I'm not gonna bend on this one. Without a promise, this is highway robbery.
I'd rather die than give my cards to a thief. Kill me if you want to. I won't open my binder again!
You're a real lunatic. But not the same kind of crazy like me.
All right. I promise then. And book!
I'm holding 131 cards. 97 are specified slot cards.
I have 102. As for specified slots, I've got 71. And book!
You have 2 and 75, right?
Yeah!
Book!
That's all I need.
Good Wren.
But it's clear he still has a long way to go.
The best defense is a strong offense. And besides, a single explosion won't be enough to finish you off.
So stay on the attack!
This kid has skill. But his use of Aura is sloppy at best.
I can't imagine why he was so confident.
You're not on his level at this point. You won't be able to do much damage.
But keep attacking anyway!
You will get hurt!
You still haven't answered my question.
Who told you about my ability?
Well, it's not important.
What I want to say is
that I don't need to use my ability to deal with you.
Exactly as planned.
Once he's seen how much stronger he is,
we'll reel him in
and spring the trap.
Us!
That's how I'd like to respond.
But I don't want to be on the losing end forever!
I'll make him use his power
and finish the plan later!
Hmm.
Looking to get hurt some more?
Use your ability!
Cause I've got a surprise for you!
I know what you're thinking.
And I won't use it!
Damn brat!
She's a lot faster than I thought.
Fuck!
She should be all out of transport spells.
What's she doing?
She used transform to disguise it as another card?
Accompany on!
Toso Frohby!
Accompany?
Why?
I don't get it.
Why did you go to all that trouble just for this?
Did you want to be alone with me or what?
Oh no.
It's quite simple, really.
I didn't want you begging your little friends for help.
Huh?
What the hell are you talking about?
Idiot.
What I'm saying is that I'm stronger than you.
Why you little...
So you call those attacks, huh?
Well, too bad, because you still can't beat me!
I won't go easy on you.
It's nothing personal.
That's exactly what I was going to say.
Huh? What?
I always let people get a hit in.
Like a tribute.
Because once I turn back,
I have a hard time restraining myself.
So I end up killing my opponents!
Oh, are you still alive?
I'm impressed.
Why would you...
hide your power if...
you're that strong?
Two reasons.
First, never show your hand.
And second, I absolutely despise my appearance!
I'm too buff and I hate it!
So do you agree or don't you?
Huh?
Guess he passed out.
I've got a slight edge in martial arts skill and physical strength,
but he has me beat in aura capacity.
So I probably won't be able to hurt him with any normal attack.
That makes him perfect to experiment on.
Damn it!
That hit just felt like a knife in my brain!
I can't afford to mess around with this guy.
Wrong!
Experiment number one!
Lightning palm!
That wasn't enough to knock him out.
But at least I can stun him for a few seconds.
Okay.
Experiment number two!
A yo-yo?
Let's go!
What is he up to?
Gah!
What the hell?
What's it made of?
It's my brother's alloy.
He came up with it himself.
Weighs around 50 kilograms.
That's a real punch.
See?
Gah!
Between the weight and centrifugal force,
that really stings.
He's got a habit of leaving his right flank exposed
when I attack a certain way.
If I could take his yo-yo
and leave him empty-handed,
he's bound to make the same mistake.
Gotcha!
Right there!
All right!
Time to crush your ribs!
Gah!
Uh-oh.
Did I forget to mention I have two yo-yos?
No.
Ugh.
Wow.
You're still conscious?
Ugh.
Hey, old man.
Did you know that when you kick me, you raise up your guard arm?
It's like you're making your own blind spot.
Ugh.
Wait.
He used my blind spot to pull out another yo-yo and attack?
Hang on.
So that means that your blocking habit was-
Was a fake to make you kick me with your left leg.
And when you released your first yo-yo?
Yeah.
I knew you picked something up to throw at me.
Why'd you use a company to draw me away?
To make you focus on a one-on-one fight and dismiss your surroundings.
I just don't believe it.
In that brief exchange, you had enough time to set three traps?
Three, huh?
You gotta be kidding me.
Every move I made was a trap.
Experiment complete.
Looks like they both work.
It's over.
Why don't you accept it?
You will never defeat me.
Shut up.
Shut up! I'm not... finished with you yet!
It seems I was wrong.
I take back what I said before. You are tough.
This is my ability. I'll show it to you.
This battle isn't only about the physical. I'm going to crush his spirit. His will to fight, to stand, and to resist.
Otherwise, he'll never admit defeat.
If I truly want to win, I can't be stubborn. I'll make him see. I'll prove to him that all his hard work and confidence mean absolutely nothing!
Here he comes!
The villain has unleashed his true power. Will Gon be able to emerge victorious?
wretched....
僕らにどんな世界が? 道なき道の先に待ってる?
声泣き声はこのまま どこにも届かずに消えてゆくの?
忘れない 昨日の日は消せない 今日の後悔も投げ捨て カムシェアに明日を目指す 朝日に照らされた傷 笑い合って 終わることない旅を続けよう
向かい風としていながら それでも進む理由がある だから友よ 置いてくためだけに生きるのはまだ 早いだろ
身につけたもの 抱え込んだもの 手放したとき 始まる何か 上手く生きてく レシピを破り捨てて 感じるリズム そう僕らのやり方で
ご視聴ありがとうございました